Kheel, Theodore W. Arbitration files 6021/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Theodore W. Kheel Arbitration files
1945-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel, Theodore W.
6021/003
30 cubic feet
30 linear ft.
Papers.
5767570
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 29, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 13, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Theodore Woodrow Kheel was said to be named for both Woodrow Wilson and his political rival Theodore Roosevelt, the result of a compromise between his politically differing parents. The settlement presaged a career in which Kheel would be tapped by mayors, governors, and presidents to settle disputes that were part of the nation's major political and social transitions from post-World War II to well into the 21st century.
Born in 1914 in Brooklyn, Ted Kheel attended public high school in the Bronx. He was awarded a Regents scholarship to Cornell University, where he attended an accelerated undergraduate law school program permitting him to earn a bachelor's and law degree in six years.
In private practice for a brief time after graduation from law school, Kheel soon was offered a position as a National Labor Relations Board attorney in Washington. Kheel's special talents as a mediator and his obvious political skills soon gave him the opportunity to move to a new war-time agency, where he was initially hired as principal mediation officer. By 1944, he had been appointed executive director of the National War Labor Board, with a staff of 2,500 who were hearing 150 disputes a week. Kheel's work at the WLB introduced him to the most important figures in the labor movement and key government officialscontacts he would use effectively in the future.
Following the end of World War II, Kheel returned to New York City and was drafted by Mayor O'Dywer to serve in the city's new Labor Relations Division, which Kheel came to head within a year. With the agreement of the mayor, Kheel was able to serve both in this position and maintain a separate, private law practice.
In 1949, Kheel was appointed to a part-time position as impartial chairman for an important segment of public transit in New York City, a position in which he would render 30,000 decisions through 1982. Also in 1949, Kheel became a partner in the New York law firm Battle, Fowler, Jaffin and Kheel. His skills in conflict resolution led an observer to remark that the firm's work began with a battle, ended by Kheel.
During his more than half a century of involvement in labor matters, Kheel was known above all else for his extraordinary ability to get feuding parties to make concessions to reach an agreement. In the important New York and national labor disputes which he would be called to mediate, Kheel's approach was to protect management rights and at the same time demand fairness to workers while also trying to protect the public interest in the issue.
Kheel's was frequently the voice of reason in settling a number of extremely difficult labor disputes of the 1960s and 1970s. Mayor Robert F. Wagner, Jr., turned to Kheel to help end the 114-day newspaper strike of 1962-63. Among his most infamous cases was the strike involving Mike Quill, head of the Transport Workers Union, who publically battled Mayor John V. Lindsay in 1965-66. Kheel's efforts also included helping coordinate bargainers and mediators during the 35-day New York City teachers' strike in 1968. President Lyndon B. Johnson summoned Kheel to Washington in 1964 to help mediate 10 days of feverish negotiations that prevented a nationwide rail walkout. Kheel would ultimately serve as a mediator and advisor for virtually every New York mayor from O'Dwyer to Beame, for the Kennedy-Johnson Administration, and other presidential administrations as well.
Kheel's interests in public issues were not limited to the labor sector. The policy disputes that came to his attention as a mediator and lawyer frequently cried out for larger solutions, and Kheel was not averse to using his considerable public presence and media contacts to seek redress, especially for what he viewed as past institutional injustices or misguided government actions. Although pressed to do so on a number of occasions, Kheel refused to run for elective office, preferring the role of a labor neutral and public advocate.
Kheel was also not averse to backing his powers of persuasion with legal action: a fierce advocate for public transit, he initiated a class action lawsuit over the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey's refusal to fund mass rail transit. His most sustained crusade for the public good related to his battle to limit commuter auto traffic and control highway building in New York City in favor of increased use of public transportation. Initially attacked by Port Authority officials and some city, state, and federal politicians of both parties, many of the solutions originally proposed by Kheel, including the concept of the subsidized fare, became public policy in later years.
An early supporter of the civil rights movement, Kheel and his wife Ann become involved with the New York Urban League in the 1950s. He served as its president in 1955 and as national president for four years. He worked with President Johnson on race issues and with Martin Luther King, Jr., in a libel suit against the New York Times. Kheel's mediation skills led to important strides in hiring African Americans in the airline industry. His reputation for sensitivity to minority issues resulted in his becoming involved in efforts to add civilians to the New York City Police Review Board in 1965. Kheel was also recruited as a peacemaker in the 1968 Ocean Hill-Brownsville Teachers dispute.
Even though Kheel handled disputes for transit workers, typesetters, and longshoremen, he reveled in the finer things in life, and dabbled as a restaurateur in fine food and was a patron of the fine arts.
He once owned a stake in Le Pavillon, a leading French restaurant in Manhattan, among others. He also represented numerous artists, including Robert Rauschenberg and Christo, and was the prime mover in the realization of the long-heralded Gates Project in Central Park in 2005.
He also made millions of dollars as an entrepreneur while facilitating sustainable economic and social change. He was the lead investor in the giant Punta Cana resort, transforming 30 miles of jungle in the Dominican Republic, and helped bring about the airport that opened that country to tourists and travelers.
Finding the solution to problems such as the impact of automation on the workplace, community disputes, and protecting a sustainable environment in which mankind will flourish, to name but a few, were the focus of Kheel's interest, enthusiasm, and financial support. He was the prime mover, bringing along like-minded citizens and specialists, in the creation of organizations to find solutions to the more intractable issues facing society. The Foundation on Employee Health, Medical Care and Welfare, the Foundation on Automation and Employment (and its British counterpart), Automation House, the Institute for Mediation and Conflict Resolution, and the Earth Pledge Foundation were among the most successful of such efforts. In the same vein, in collaboration with Price, Waterhouse in 1994, Kheel formed Prevention and Early Resolution of Conflicts, Inc. (PERC), now housed at Cornell ILR as Cornell/PERC Institute.
A prolific writer, Kheel is perhaps best known for his encyclopedic work on labor law. Throughout a career that was active almost until his death at age 96 in November 2010, he was able to balance, with amazing success, advocacy of the public good and the management of a successful law and mediation practice and other business and cultural interests.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5024: Theodore W. Kheel Arbitration Awards 5776 AV: Theodore W. Kheel Interviews and Programs 6017: Theodore W. Kheel Newspaper Clipping File 6021 AV: Theodore W. Kheel Audio-Visual Materials 6021 MB: Theodore W. Kheel Memorabilia 6021 P: Theodore W. Kheel Photographs 6021/001: Theodore W. Kheel Correspondence 6021/004: Theodore W. Kheel Legal Files 6021/005: Theodore W. Kheel Speeches and Articles 6021/006: Theodore W. Kheel Non-Profit Organization Files 6021/007: Theodore W. Kheel Subject Files 6021/008: Theodore W. Kheel Books and Articles 6021/009: Theodore W. Kheel Newspaper Clipping File 6021/010: Theodore W. Kheel Additional Files 6021/011: Theodore W. Kheel Punta Cana Files 6021/012m: Invitation and Program for the Theodore W. Kheel Memorial Service 6059 OH: Thomas Shactman Interviews with Theodore W. Kheel 6194 OH: College of Labor and Employment Lawyers Interview with Theodore W. Kheel 6196 OH: New York City Central Labor Council Interview of Theodore W. Kheel for Central Archives 6207 OH: CLEL Video Oral History Project
Kheel, Theodore Woodrow
5767570
- Arbitration Lists, 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor coach Employees of America AFL-CIO Division 589 and Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Jan 29
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor coach employees of America, AFL division 726 and NYC Transit authority, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Oct 24
- Local 726, Amal. Assoc. of Street, electric railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America and NYC Transit Authority, Richard Konecny, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Dec 4
- Local 726, Amal. Assoc. of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach employees of America and NYC Transit Authority, Charles DiCarlo, et al., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Oct 5
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor coach Employees of America, AFL-CIO division 726 and NYC Transit Authority, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Jan 1
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor coach employees of America, AFL-CIO division 726 and NYCTA, 1960- 1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Jan 1, 1960 - Dec 31, 1961
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor coach employees of America AFL-CIO division 726 and New York city Transit Authority, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America AFL-CIO Division 726 and New York City, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor coach employees of America, AFL Division 1056 and NYC Transit Authority, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach employees of America, AFL-CIO division 1056 and NYC Transit Authority, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America Local 1056 and NYCTA - Michael D'Amico (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America, AFL-CIO Division 1056 and NYC Transit Authority (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America AFL-CIO division 1056 and New York City Transit Authority, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America AFL-CIO division 1056 and New York City Transit Authority, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America and Children's Bus Service Local 1181, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Feb 1
- Local 589, amalgamated Transit Union, AFL-CIO and Mass. Bay Transportation Authority, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  July 15
- Amalgamated Transit Union AFL-CIO Division 726 and New York City Transit Authority, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Transit Union AFL-CIO division 726 and New York city Transit Authority, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- ATU Local 726 (Leaman Hall) and NYCTA, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Nov 15
- ATU Local 726 and NYCTA - Charles Medity, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- ATU Local 726 (Pasquale Alfano, et al.) and NYCTA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  April 26
- ATU Local 726 (Richard Marceante et al.) and NYCTA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  June 27
- ATU Local 726 (Joseph Cognato, et al.) and NYCTA, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Dec 13, 1979 - April 29, 1980
- ATU Local 726 - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  July 1980 - September 1982
- ATU Local 726 vs. New York City Transit Authority - Robert Landry, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Feb 9
- ATU Local 726 vs. New York City Transit Authority Jams Kerrigan, et al., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  June 5
- ATU Local 1056 (Sol Cohen et al.) and NYCTA, 1964-1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Amalgamated Transit Union AFL-CIO Division 1056 and New York City Transit Authority, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Local 1056, and NYC Transit Authority, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  May 23
- Amalgamated Transit Union AFL-CIO Division 1056 and New York city Transit Authority, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- ATU Local 1056 (Joseph Maletta, et al.) and NYCTA, 1968-1976 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  May 14. 1968 - Dec 8, 1976
- ATU Local 1056 (Marisa Kahn, et al.) and NYCTA, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  July 24
- ATU Local 1056 (John Jackson, et al.) and NYCTA, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Dec 6
- ATU Local 1056 (Dale Williams, et al.) and NYCTA, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  May 16
- ATU Local 1056 (Donald Duncan and Michael Penoro) and NYCTA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- ATU Local 1056 (Leonard Chumsky, et al.) and NYCTA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- ATU Local 1056 (Kenneth Johnston) and NYCTA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  May 24
- ATU Local 1056 (Sherman Phelan, et al.) and NYCTA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  June 29
- ATU Local 1056 (Peter Brunie) and NYCTA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  Dec 13
- ATU 1056 (John Wiliis ) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  March 26
- ATU Local 1056 (Martin Hard, et al.) and NYCTA, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  June 8
- ATU Local 1056 and NYCTA - Harvey McKenzie, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  July 22
- ATU Local 1056 (Sherman De Lautch, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  March 22
- NYCTA and ATU Local 1056 - Anthony Mariano, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  Nov 4
- ATU Local 1061 (Nicholas Autumnio) and Schenck corp., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  April 9
- ATU Local 1061 (William Harrison) and Schenck Corporation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  Aug 27
- ATU Local 1061 (Richard Corpac) and Schenck Corp., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  Jan 15
- ATU Local 1061 and Schenck Corp., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  Oct 26
- ATU Local 1061 and Schenck Corp., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  May 19
- ATU Local 1061 and Schenck Corp., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  June 21
- ATU Local 1061 and Schenck Corp., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Mar 20
- ATU Local 1061 and Schenck corp., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ATU Local 1061 and Schenck Corp., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  July 7
- ATU Local 1061 and Schenck corp., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Aug 24
- ATU Local 1179 (Silbert Sron) and Green Bar Liner, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Oct 15
- ATU Local 1179 and Green Bus Line - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Publication, 1967-1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  May 4, 1967 - April 1, 1980
- ATU Local 1179 (John Ranello, et al.) and Green Bus Line, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  May 12
- ATU Local 1179 (Sherman Bender) and Green Bus Lines, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Jan 7
- ATU local 1061 and Schenck Corp. - Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  May 18, 1969 - June 20, 1968
- ATU Local 1179 and Green Bus Lines, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Mar 31, 1969- May 8, 1969
- ATU Local 1179 (Stanley Maier) and Green Bus Lines, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  May 20
- ATU Local 1179 (James Sherman) and Green Bus Lines, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Dec 7
- ATU Local 1179 (M. Jergenbaum, et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Dec 14
- ATU Local 1179 (Alfred Nolan) and Green Bus Lines, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ATU Local 1179 (Levis Glover, et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Oct 29
- ATU Local 1179 (Harry Oater, et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- ATU Local 1179 (William Krueger, et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  April 4
- ATU Local 1179 and Green Bus Lines, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Jan 27
- ATU Local 1179 (Sherman Ahearn) and Green Bus Lines, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  May 6
- ATU Local 1179 (Robert Mister, et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Sept 27
- ATU Local 1179 (Aynello Juciello, et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Sept 8
- ATU Local 1179 (John Paolella, et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Nov 21
- ATU Local 1179 and Green Bus Lines, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- ATU Local 1179 (Sinclair Rivers) and Green bus Lines, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  March 31
- ATU Local 1179 and Green Bus Lines, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- ATU Local 1179 (Dennis Morgan, et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Sept 15
- ATU Local 1179 and Green Bus Lines - Anthony Procida, et al., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Jan 28
- ATU Local 1179 (Stephen Dash et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- ATU Local 1179 (Ronald McKean) and Green Bus Lines, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Jan 30
- ATU Local 1179 (Sherman Bonsignire) and Green Bus Lines, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Aug 19
- ATU Local 1179 (Sharon Johnson, et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  Oct 9
- ATU 1179 (John Saluto) and Green Bus Lines, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  April 24
- ATU Local 1179 (Joseph Pannell) and Green Bus Lines, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  May 28
- ATU 1179 (Kenneth Ruggiero) and Green Bus Lines, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Sept 3
- ATU Local 1179 (Walter Grecky) and Green Bus Lines, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  July 29
- ATU Local 1179 (Peter Hubbard) and Green Bus Lines, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  Sept 30
- ATU Local 1179 (Stephen P., et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  Sept 13
- ATU Local 1179 (Robert Reidbinger) and Green Bus Lines, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  Jan 22
- ATU Local 1179 and Green Bus Lines - Cassmore Bernard, et al., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- ATU 1179 (Peter J.) and Green Bus Lines, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  March 1
- ATU Local 1179 (Robert Geist) and Green Bus Lines, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- ATU Local 1179 (Daniel and David Ugiliabro) and Green Bus Lines, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  Jan 6
- ATU Local 1179 (Rafael Guzman, et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- ATU Local 1179 (John Pizzeria, et al.) and Green Bus Lines, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  May 14
- division of ATU NY Employees Pension Plan Impasse of the Trustees, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- ATU Local 1181 and Children's Bus Service Line, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  Feb 14, 1964 - April 15, 1965
- ATU Local 1181 and Children's Bus Services, Inc., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  Dec 15
- ATU Local 1181 and Children's Bus Service, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  Feb 26
- ATU Local 1181 and Children's Bus Services Inc., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- ATU Local 1181 (Samuel Lain, et al.) and City - Wide Transportation, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Sept 18
- ATU Local 1181 and Metro Suburban Bus Authority - William Young, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Jan 10
- ATU Local 1181 (Anthony DeNardo et al.) and Pioneer Bus Corp., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Aug 15
- ATU Local 1181 and Pioneer Transportation, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Nov 5
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Stuart Stein) and ACJ Transportation, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Sept 23
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Douglas Bogle) and All American School, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  April 13
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Charles Phoenix) and All-State Transit Co., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Hope Scott) and All Ways Transportation (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Oct 15, 1992 - Nov 30, 1992
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Russel Vulpio) and All-Ways Transportation, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  June 13
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Pierre Jean-Pierre) and All Ways Transportation, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  April 16
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Arnell Metayer) and Amboy Bus co., 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Feb 20
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Blanca Lopez) and Amboy Bus Co., 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  April 8
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Hazel Robinson) and Amboy Bus co., 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Amboy Bus Co. - 1994-1977 Collective Bargaining Agreement (Box 3, Folder 14)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Marco DiAntonio) and Amboy Bus Co., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  May 25
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Donald Sehested) and Amboy Bus Co., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Oct 30
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Michele Pratt) and Amboy Bus Co., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  April 23
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Amboy Bus Co., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Henry Spencer) and Amboy Bus Co., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Aug 1
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Gilbert Jackson, et al.) and American Bus company, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  June 20
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Marcelin Villasson, et al.) and Atlantic Express, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Oct 28
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Sylvester Lindsay) and Barone Transportation, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  aug 5
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Fred Leite) and Beamer Transit, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  May 13
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Willie McCullough) and Bobby Bus Co., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  June 26
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Emerald Johnson) and Bobby's Bus Co., Inc., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  July 28
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Arthur Canestro) and Carant Bus Co., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Nov 27
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Peter Scala) and Caravan Coach Corp., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Aug 11
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Gustavo Sepulveda) and Caravan Coach Corp., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  June 11
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Angela Passaro) and Caravan Transportation, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  May 17
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Brenda Wright) and Carl's Car Service, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  Oct 20
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Carl's Escort Service, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  July 1
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Sabrena Ford) and Children's Bus Service, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  July 13
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Citywide Transit - Oscar Memory, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  Jan 9
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Colonial Bus Co., Inc., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  Sept 22
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Benjamin DuBose) and Colonial Transit, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  Jan 18, 1982 - Feb 17, 1983
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Colonial Transit, Inc., 1982 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Roberto Meier) and colonial Transportation, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  June 1, 1995 - Nov 18, 1996
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Nicholas Panagoupalos) and Command Bus company, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  Aug 12
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (John Jesoviero) and Command Bus Company, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  Oct 6
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Mike Biscotti) and Command Bus Company, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Anthony Chuisano, et al.) and Command Bus Company, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (David Hamilton) and command bus co., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  Sept 17
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Stanley Gay) and Command Bus Company, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  Sept 21
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Guillermo Diaz) and Dand J School Bus, Inc., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  Jan 31
- ATU Local 1181-1061 and Domar Buses, Inc. - Allen Karlsberg, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  Nov 9
- ATU local 1181-1061 (Joseph Gendeh) and D.T. Transportation, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- ATU Local 1181-1061 ( Earl Caldwell, et al.) and Evergreen Bus Service, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  March 21 - May 3
- ATU Local 1181-1061 (Raymond Cush) and Evergreen Bus Service, Inc., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 48)